## Fabio Di Pane

Italian | date of birth 01/11/1983

Tel. +39 3927464155

Via Andrea Palladio 41 35134 – Padua, Italy



dipane.fabio@gmail.com

#### Summary

After a career in the economic/touristic sector, I intend to relocate to IT, my passion since the age of 5, with the goal of becoming Front-End / Web Developer at first, to then expand my knowledge and studies also to the Back-end, Software development or what the future challenges will require of me.

Since 2015 I have been studying assiduously through various US E-Learning courses such as HarvardX CS50, Android Basics Nanodegree by Google, CodeAcademy, freeCodeCamp (continuously deepening languages like Python3, SQLite, HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript and several of its frameworks, Jinja3 and others), with the purpose of improving my coding skills and always keeping up with the modern technologies and skills required by the market.

Continuously updated and curious to learn everything that has to do with coding, currently I've started to study for the <u>Cisco CCNA 200-125</u> and I'm deepening my Python knowledge to enhance my networking skills. I am <u>open to learn any language proposed</u>. The links to my Portfolio can be found in the "Known Technologies" section.

# Working Experience

Web Master, Social Media Manager at Il Rosmarino fattoria didattica

01/2016 - 12/2016

Web page maintenance and management, events and social media management. Suspended activity in order to be able to devote more time to study.

#### Australia

02/2013 - 01/2014

After having traveled all over the country working in several companies, including communication companies, I had the opportunity to gain experience in working environments different from those I was used to and to deepen my knowledge of English.

## General Manager, Destination Manager, Social-media Manager, Booking Manager at La Darsena Viaggi by TUVIAGGI SRL

06/2011 - 07/2012

Travel planning management (South America and North Africa), communication, booking, customer care

## Intern at Backpackers World

09/2010 - 01/2011

Support in travel planning, communication, booking, customer care.

## Hotel Receptionist and Catering service at Several Companies

09/2001 - Present

Alongside my professional career, I have constantly worked in the catering sector to be able to financially support my training costs.

#### Education

HarvardX: CS50

### Introduction to Computer Science

2017 - 2019

E-learning training path created by Harvard University, aimed, through various programming languages (C, Python, Javascript and others) and challenges to be faced, to provide the bases and cognitive mechanisms for the creation of efficient and effective programs and algorithms.

#### **Challenges Portfolio:**

https://github.com/submit50/saylos

#### **Certificate of Achievement:**

https://courses.edx.org/certificates/f52033a388ed494db1a96cdd6c86edbc

## freeCodeCamp - Full-stack developer certificate

2015 - Present

US E-learning training course freeCodeCamp.

#### Portfolio:

https://codepen.io/saylos/ https://www.freecodecamp.org/saylos

#### **Responsive Web Design Certificate:**

https://www.freecodecamp.org/certification/saylos/responsive-web-design

#### **JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures Certificate:**

https://www.freecodecamp.org/certification/saylos/javascript-algorithms-and-data-structures

02/2010 - 07/2010

Master Degree at CTS Study Center, Rome.

## Bachelor Degree in Economics and Management of Touristic Services

09/2001 - 11/2008

At Cà Foscari University, Venice.

## Known Technologies

## OS: Linux, Windows

I've been using bash and Linux Distros for more than 20 years.

HTML5, CSS3, Sass, Bootstrap, Flexbox, CSS Grid, JavaScript ES6, jQuery, Jinja3, SQLite, Python3, Git, GitHub. Currently Studying Angular, React, Redux.

In continuous study and improvement.

#### Portfolio:

**GitHub**: https://github.com/saylos **Codepen**: https://codepen.io/saylos/

CS50-GitHub: https://github.com/submit50/saylos

VS Code, Atom, Eclipse, GIMP, Inkscape, LibreOffice, Office365 (Word, Excell), Google Analytics, Google Apps.

Photo / logo editing, tools for work organization and software development.

### Languages

	Reading	Written	Spoken
English	C1	C1	C1
	advanced	advanced	advanced
Spanish	C1	B1	B2
	advanced	intermediate	good